bayareamommy.net 2019-05-01

# Privacy Policy - Bay Area Mommy

**Collecting information**  
We collect information from you when you subscribe to our newsletter or fill out a form. When ordering or registering on our site, as appropriate, you may be asked to enter your name or e-mail address. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

**Using information  
**Any of the information we collect from you may be used to administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site feature, and to send periodic emails. The email address you provide may be used to send you information, respond to inquiries, and/or other requests or questions.

**Protecting information**  
We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you enter, submit, or access your personal information.

**Cookies**  
We do not use cookies.

**Disclosure to third parties**  
We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our site policies, or protect our or others’ rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

**Third party links**  
Occasionally, at our discretion, we may include or offer third party products or services on our website. These third party sites have separate and independent privacy policies. We therefore have no responsibility or liability for the content and activities of these linked sites. Nonetheless, we seek to protect the integrity of our site and welcome any feedback about these sites.

**California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

**Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance**  
We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

**Your Consent**  
By using our site, you consent to our privacy policy.

**Changes to our Privacy Policy**  
If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, send an email notifying you of any changes, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below.

This policy was last modified on August 2, 2012.

**Contacting Us**  
If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below. Alternatively, you may also use our Contact Form.

http://BayAreaMommy.net

1580 Meadow Ridge Cir  
San Jose, CA 95131  
alice@bayareamommy.net

This policy is powered by Trust Guard, [PCI compliance scans](http://www.trust-guard.com/PCI-Compliance-s/65.htm)[follow](http://www.bayareamommy.net/privacy-policy/# "Toggle link-love \(currently "follow"\). Only admins see this.").
